[{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":10057,"timeElapsed":124153},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5133,"timeElapsed":129288},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":132169},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":9741,"timeElapsed":141913},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5966,"timeElapsed":147881},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5047,"timeElapsed":152930},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3563,"timeElapsed":156495},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":49856,"timeElapsed":206352},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4077,"timeElapsed":210432},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":55085,"timeElapsed":268391},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3318,"timeElapsed":271711},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3805,"timeElapsed":275518},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3825,"timeElapsed":279344},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4342,"timeElapsed":283688},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":26790,"timeElapsed":310480},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4574,"timeElapsed":315055},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3647,"timeElapsed":318703},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3031,"timeElapsed":321736},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":13222,"timeElapsed":336344},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7239,"timeElapsed":343584},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2949,"timeElapsed":346535},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":58442,"timeElapsed":404979},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":407677},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":411023},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3432,"timeElapsed":414457},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4437,"timeElapsed":418896},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1669,"timeElapsed":420567},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8862,"timeElapsed":430302},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2278,"timeElapsed":432582},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2351,"timeElapsed":434934},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638365,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3607,"timeElapsed":438543},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980642117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3750,"timeElapsed":442295},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2391,"timeElapsed":444688},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2764,"timeElapsed":447454},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980650556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":450734},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":453455},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2245,"timeElapsed":455702},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980660157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":460334},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":462728},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2484,"timeElapsed":465214},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9103,"timeElapsed":474318},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980676277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2135,"timeElapsed":476455},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5350,"timeElapsed":481807},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2278,"timeElapsed":484087},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5558,"timeElapsed":489646},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":491807},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715243,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":22581,"timeElapsed":515421},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3200,"timeElapsed":518622},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":8373,"timeElapsed":526997},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2919,"timeElapsed":529918},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6393,"timeElapsed":536312},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5716,"timeElapsed":542029},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980745117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3265,"timeElapsed":545295},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4741,"timeElapsed":550038},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980751780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1918,"timeElapsed":551958},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":558206},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760387,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2357,"timeElapsed":560565},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763268,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2880,"timeElapsed":563446},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":565966},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2302,"timeElapsed":568270},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2502,"timeElapsed":570774},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1869,"timeElapsed":572645},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777387,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4917,"timeElapsed":577565},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"246","question":"Do you use social media sites or apps? If so, which ones and why? If not, why not?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":579668},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6883,"timeElapsed":587485},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1968,"timeElapsed":589455},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980791116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1837,"timeElapsed":591294},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2903,"timeElapsed":594198},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980796468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":596646},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3327,"timeElapsed":599974},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802220,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2421,"timeElapsed":602398},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980804735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2513,"timeElapsed":604913},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980878123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":73387,"timeElapsed":678301},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2254,"timeElapsed":680558},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980899491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":7755,"timeElapsed":699669},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5704,"timeElapsed":705374},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":708878},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980930956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":22255,"timeElapsed":731134},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933675,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2716,"timeElapsed":733853},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980955556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":21878,"timeElapsed":755734},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":758949},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":12118,"timeElapsed":771070},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980973321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2427,"timeElapsed":773499},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9261,"timeElapsed":783693},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":3446,"timeElapsed":787141},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5015,"timeElapsed":792158},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3229,"timeElapsed":795390},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2805,"timeElapsed":798198},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981001219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3197,"timeElapsed":801397},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981003242,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2021,"timeElapsed":803420},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2575,"timeElapsed":805997},{"subjectID":"ub2z6e9q8e","prolificID":"5de3c83c2033793be6591e53","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2615459cc633fef911d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981008020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":808198}]